[theme music playing]
[Jepoy] Will you just stand there
while Ivy and Arnaldo get married?!
[Ivy] Jepoy, shouldn't you be
the one who understands the most
why I need to marry Arnaldo?!
[Jepoy] I'll support her plan.
But I'll find another way
to bring down the Ardientes.
I would like you to take care
of one of our enemies.
Kill Jaguar.
For the sake of our family.
[Raul] So, you're really
going to kill Jaguar?
Can you do it?
Ping!
[Emilia] Who are you?!
[grunts]
[Raul] Rufo, I need your help.
[Emilia] Where were you?
[Raul] I'm right here, taking a bath.
[Anthony] Thank you for coming here today
for the Poblacion Ardiente public debate.
You haven't been in any
government position before.
Wouldn't it be better
if our lives all improved together?
[Anthony] You are running out
of time, Mayor.
Mayor!
[Ivy] I think it's time the public learns
that my future husband
is going through something.
What do you mean? Is the mayor sick?
[Ivy] I guess that's all
I can say for now.
[Julio] Tell me the truth.
What happened, that you had
to walk out during the debate?
Please tell me.
[Arnaldo] They're in front of me.
Carlotta and Nimfa…
They're haunting me!
They're alive!
I don't know what's happening!
I don't know!
I… I don't know what to do!
[Arnaldo crying]
It's okay. It's all right.
-Grandpa.
-Go and rest.
-But… [sniffles]
Go and rest. Go to your bed.
-[Arnaldo sobs]
-Sleep.
We'll talk again tomorrow, all right?
Don't worry. I'll be here.
I'll be here for you.
I will always be here for you, okay?
Stop crying. Come on, my son.
Come on.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Tomorrow is another day.
Forget it. Forget it.
Forget it.
Forget it. They're not real.
[sighs]
Forget it.
Go ahead.
Go. We'll talk again.
Everything will be different.
Everything will be fine tomorrow.
It's okay.
-It's okay, my son. It's okay.
-[Arnaldo sniffles]
Go and rest.
[breath quivering]
[sobbing]
[tense music playing]
Who are you?
Speak up.
I just got lost.
[tense music playing]
Got lost?
All right, leave.
Turn around.
[tense music playing]
Scram.
Leave!
Just so you know,
the first two private
investigators I hired
now both have permanent residency in hell.
I'm sure you don't want
to join them, do you?
Now, what's the dirt on Lily Cruz?
She's spotless, Ma'am Emilia.
What do you mean?
She really is Lily Cruz.
She's a high school teacher
in some province.
She's an active member
of her town's organization.
She's an exemplary citizen.
And other than that,
what else did you find
about that Lily Cruz?
What distracted my son during the debate?
[tense music playing]
She's an orphan.
Her aunt, who worked overseas,
raised her for 10 years.
When the woman died,
Lily Cruz inherited everything she owned.
Oh, so she has no family.
Now, it makes sense.
That's why she can afford
to dress herself properly.
So…
When did this aunt die?
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
Jepoy.
Ivy.
Jepoy, I need your help.
What's wrong?
It's Emilia.
She's doing a background check on Anna
because she thinks Anna did something
to cause Arnaldo
to walk out of the debate.
Don't worry about it.
Before we even came back,
I took care of Anna's background.
They won't find anything
about her real identity.
Thank you, Jepoy.
I know I can always count on you,
even if you don't agree
with my plan right now.
Ivy…
It doesn't matter what I think or feel.
You know I'll always support you.
But you'll have to forgive me.
I'll keep finding another way.
Thanks.
[tense music playing]
Emilia?
Ivy.
Thanks for the statement
you released to the press
about Arnaldo, by the way.
At least now, people know
he's not feeling well.
But, on the other hand, with what you did,
people might think that he's weak.
No, that's not necessarily the case.
It could've helped him gain
the support of the voters.
Did I just hear you talking
to a private investigator?
You're doing a background check
on Lily Cruz?
[tense music playing]
Do you think he's right about
Lily Cruz's real identity?
It doesn't matter if he is, Emilia.
Or whether Lily's a friend or a foe.
Because, at the end of the day,
you've got the upper hand.
You just have to be aligned
with the right people.
And that's me.
So you're saying…
What I'm saying,
is that I'll take care of Lily Cruz.
I'll keep an eye on her.
You focus on yourself.
People are starting to notice
how Lily Cruz
has stressed you out.
And that won't be good
for Arnaldo's campaign.
Think about it.
Speaking of my future husband,
I'm going to his room.
Excuse me.
Okay.
Madam, someone sent you these.
What are you looking at?! Leave! Go!
So nosy!
[tense music playing]
[chuckles]
[giggles]
Oh, Jaguar.
Everyone, look!
Another point for Team Diego.
-That's right!
-Yeah!
-[cheering]
-[applause]
My Diego is just that good!
That's how it is
when one is sincere about serving others,
and when one has no hidden agenda.
You'll know he's sincere.
It'll come out naturally!
That just proves that
experience isn't enough
to dictate who a leader is supposed to be.
-That's right!
-Correct!
Mayor Arnaldo may be experienced,
but he's spent most of his term
making others suffer.
-That's true.
-Right?
-Right you are, Lily.
-Exactly.
Diego, congratulations again!
But we still have to be careful, though.
The Ardientes won't give up that easily.
They'll do everything
to make themselves look good.
Remember the peace agreement
and the press conference?
[Marlon] Just like Arnaldo
and Ivy Aguas' wedding
being held in the middle
of the campaign period.
I'm sure it's a gimmick to get more votes!
I don't even understand how that Ivy Aguas
became so close with the Ardientes.
I remember how she and Diego
used to be so close!
I don't get it, either!
It's too bad they grew apart.
But, you know what, I'm sure the Ardientes
are going to use Ivy
in every gimmick they've got.
[unsettling music playing]
You know, someone's really
messing up my son's head.
I don't know if it's that
Ivy Aguas or Lily Cruz.
I really have to find out.
I know we can't trust
Ivy Aguas completely.
But I'm just concerned, Emilia.
What if Arnaldo really has a problem?
Maybe he is…
What problem?
Are you trying to say that
Arnaldo is sick in the head?
-Of course not.
-Are you implying that?
How dare you say that about your own son?
All right. I'm sorry.
But what are you going to do now?
What's your plan?
Well, somewhere, someone is laughing
and I have to stop it.
[tense music playing]
Nice flowers there. You bought them?
No.
Who gave it to you?
Someone who's very special.
-[Raul scoffs]
-Someone who knows…
how to appreciate me and values me.
Do you have a problem with that?
No, but I'm sure Jaguar sent you that.
If I see that bastard,
I'll be sure to break his mask
and his face too. You'll see.
And so?
At least Jaguar gives me flowers.
Unlike you,
who can't even give me
a nice funeral wreath!
Here we go again.
[unsettling music playing]
[muffled screams]
[heavy breathing]
No!
No! No! No!
[Arnaldo screaming]
[sobbing]
[screaming]
Make it stop!
Please!
Please stop!
Please make it stop!
Stop it!
Please!
Please, stop!
Hon?!
-Hon? Hon!
-Make it stop!
-Hon, look at me!
-Please make it stop.
-Shh.
-Stop it!
-Please!
-Hon!
Hon, calm down!
Make it stop!
-Hon, I'm here!
-Make it stop!
-[Arnaldo screaming]
-[Julio sobbing]
-Stop it!
-Hon!
-Make it stop!
-Hon, be strong!
-Why?
-Stop!
-Why?!
-Make it stop!
[Arnaldo screaming]
Make it stop! [sobbing]
[Ivy's breath hitches]
Who did this to you?!
Tell me!
[Arnaldo wailing]
-Make it stop!
-Hon!
Make it stop!
-Make what stop.
-What do you mean?
-Make it stop!
-What?
Please!
Stop it!
[Arnaldo continues wailing]
Hon, hon!
-Stop it!
-Hon…
What are you seeing?
Why?
-[stifled cries]
-[faint screaming]
No.
No…
No!
Not him. Not him!
-Hon.
-[Arnaldo crying]
-Hon, enough.
-Stop it!
[uncontrollable screaming]
[Arnaldo] Please, stop!
Ivy?
Shh.
What was that sound?
Huh?
What sound?
I heard him shouting. It was so loud.
Shouting?
Arnaldo's been sleeping
this whole time, Emilia.
Maybe you were dreaming.
Hmm.
-Okay.
-All right.
-Go back to bed.
-Good night.
Good night.
[door closes]
[dark music playing]
Are these the places
we haven't visited yet?
Yes, ma'am.
-Ah, okay.
-[phone ringing]
Excuse me.
Hello? Lily, sweetie?
Mom?
[Camia sighs] How are you there?
Are you at the Ardientes'?
Yes, Mom. I'm here.
I miss you so much.
Mom, I miss you too.
So much, Mom.
Lily, about what happened to Arnaldo
during the debate earlier…
Did you do that?
That was all me.
Please be careful, okay?
If there's one thing
I don't want to happen,
it's you being caught up in danger.
Thank you, Mom.
But that won't ever happen.
I'm doing fine, Mom.
If you could only see Arnaldo…
[snickers]
All my plans are about to unfold.
It's just a matter of time.
It's so close now.
What do you mean by that?
Just always be careful, okay?
I will, Mom. I promise.
I'll always be careful.
Bye, Lily.
[unsettling music playing]
Diego, congratulations.
You did great during the debate.
You outwitted Arnaldo.
Thank you.
[soft music playing]
How are you?
Aren't you having a hard time?
When you faced Emilia…
you convinced her
that you really are Lily Cruz.
When Lily and I were kids,
she was like my big sister.
She was my best friend.
She'd even prioritize my
welfare and Jepoy's over hers.
Diego, this is the only way
for me to repay her
for all the sacrifices she made for us.
I'm only doing what's right.
This is for Lily and Aunt Carlotta's sake.
[Diego] Anna, thank you very much.
Thank you for helping Ivy in her mission.
And I assure you…
I'll always be here to protect you.
Just like I promised to Ivy.
[soft guitar music playing]
[phone ringing]
-Diego?
-Ivy?
Diego, we need to talk.
Okay.
Anna, I need to go.
To Ivy, right?
Okay. Be careful, all right?
And tell her I said hi.
Okay.
Hey, Jepoy.
Anna, I'll go inside.
Wait. Hold on.
I didn't see you all day,
and you won't even talk to me?
Where have you been?
Have you talked to Ivy yet?
Mm-hm.
Well, are you still upset
because she's going to marry Arnaldo?
[sighs]
Anna…
I can't stop Ivy's plans.
I'm just figuring out
another way to help her.
All right?
Get some rest, hmm?
Okay.
-Ivy.
-Diego.
How are you?
I'm okay.
Congratulations.
You did great at the debate.
Thank you for your support.
Whatever happened to Arnaldo…
I know you were behind it.
Ivy, what you're doing is dangerous.
Be careful.
Thank you, Diego.
I am being cautious.
Slowly, but surely…
my plans are unfolding.
But this isn't the end of it.
What more will you do?
[unsettling music playing]
[dark music playing]
Good morning, hon!
I'm glad you're awake now.
Here, I made you breakfast.
How did you sleep?
Hon?
Hon.
Did you…
Did you see something there last night?
-Up there.
-Where?
Up there, it was hanging up there.
Up there on the ceiling.
Something hanging from the ceiling?
Yeah, up there.
I think…
I think it looked like…
It looked like who?
Who did it look like, hon?
Who did you see?
Who?
Uh…
[sighs]
[chuckles]
Hon, maybe you just had a nightmare.
Just forget about it.
Don't mind it, hon.
Let's just get ready
for your campaign later.
So, eat your breakfast.
I'll just go to the restroom.
Okay?
Good morning.
[ominous music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Prepare 20 million pesos…
Arnaldo Ardiente.
Do it if you don't want
your dirty secrets to be exposed.
Twenty million pesos? Are you crazy?
If you're threatening me…
I'm not afraid of you.
If you're joking, it's not even funny.
Twenty million pesos, Mayor.
Bring it to the plaza…
within an hour.
How about I trace this call?
I'll hunt you down…
and kill you. How's that sound?
[sinister laughter]
You'll regret this.
-I will kill--
-[line drops]
Hello?
Hello?!
-Hell--
-[door opening]
Hon?
Who were you talking to?
My staff.
You need more bodyguards for
our grassroots project later.
Oh.
Thanks, hon.
Anyway…
It's hot, hon. I'll go take a shower.
Okay?
[tense music playing]
Wanna join, hon?
Well, we'll see Diego again
at the campaign later.
So, I want you to, uh…
[shower running]
[glass breaking]
[ominous music playing]
[mouthing] Ivy?
[shower running]
Ivy?
[ominous music]
[shower running]
Ivy?
-[shower running]
-[ominous music playing]
[ominous music continues]
[shower continues running]
[phone ringing]
Where's Ivy?
[man] I warned you, didn't I?
You will regret this.
Where's Ivy?!
[sinister laughter]
Relax.
You will get back…
what I took if you do as I say.
But if you don't…
Ivy Aguas will die.
You bastard!
[sinister laughter]
[mouthing] I will kill you.
Diego.
Have you met with Lily yet?
We talked earlier.
She told me she had a plan
to corner Arnaldo.
Do you know anything about this?
Yes, Auntie.
The last time we spoke, she told me…
that she'd need my help.
Is that so?
I hope for the best.
Diego, I fear something bad
might happen to her.
Auntie, don't worry.
I'll always remind her.
[unsettling music playing]
Ivy.
[mumbling] Ivy… Where is Ivy?
Ivy… Ivy… Ivy…
[mysterious caller] You'll regret this.
[Ivy] I'll just go to the restroom.
Good morning.
Ivy.
[suspenseful music playing]
Wanna join me, hon?
Well, we'll see Diego again
at the campaign.
Ivy…
Ivy, where are you?
Ivy?
[panting]
Ivy.
[panicked breathing]
[groans]
You'll regret this.
It's hot, hon. I'll go take a shower.
-Twenty million pesos, Mayor.
-Wanna join me, hon?
-[sinister laughter]
-Ivy Aguas will die.
Ivy… Ivy…
Thank you.
Ivy? Ivy?
-Ivy?
-Hey!
Arnaldo!
My grandson! Come here.
Join me for breakfast.
Come on!
I have things to tell you.
Oh?
Did you just wake up?
You haven't even showered. Sit down.
Sit down!
Come on.
-[Arnaldo coughs]
-Uh…
Is there any problem?
-Problem?
-Yeah.
-Nothing.
-Okay.
-Anyway, as I was telling you.
You know, I realized, after we spoke,
I realized you were right.
You were right, Arnaldo.
We can fix this situation.
To ensure your win…
You have to--
Arnaldo, listen to me!
You have to push through with the wedding.
-Okay.
-You know what…
With all the preparations,
in a couple of weeks, you can get married.
And you know how Filipinos are.
You know how we are! We're romantic!
Filipinos adore love stories!
They love fairy tales and happy endings!
And people who are getting married
are perceived to be better
at things they do.
They're perceived to be
more efficient at work.
And if that's how the people think,
they're certainly going to vote for you!
We are going to win this battle.
Now, join me here.
We have a wedding to plan.
I mean, not just a wedding, but--
Let's plan out every detail!
You know what?
You better call Ivy here too!
She needs to be here for this!
This is going to be good.
Ivy…
Yeah, call her.
She went home.
She… She went home?
She went home. I'll go get her.
You know, that's good.
All right. You go do that.
Tell her we're planning something.
I'll wait. I'll wait.
It's okay.
[unsettling music playing]
Guard!
Did you see anyone here?
Anyone suspicious?
Someone you don't know?
No, Mayor. I didn't see anyone.
How about Ivy?
Did you see her come out?
Did you see her leave?
-I didn't, sir.
-What are we paying you for?!
To just stand there and flirt
with all the maids?!
You're useless! Out of the way!
-[car engine revving]
-[unsettling music playing]
[tires screeching]
Watch where you're going!
You could've killed us!
[unsettling music playing]
Mayor Arnaldo!
Papa, where is Arnaldo?
I can't have a family meeting
without the future governor.
Arnaldo is with Ivy.
By the way…
Didn't I tell you…
to kill Jaguar?
[tense music playing]
What happened?
Have you done the deed yet?
No, Papa.
You know, we have a real problem at hand.
I mean, now that the
campaign is ongoing, and…
Diego is leading…
I cannot afford…
to let Jaguar and Diego combine forces.
That cannot be.
So, what do you think we should do?
If Emilia couldn't kill Jaguar,
then we should get him on our side.
It's like making a deal with a devil.
[tense music playing]
There is only one devil in Ardiente.
The rest are…
pawns and spineless goody-goody gum drops.
If Jaguar wants his syndicate to survive…
I am the devil that he should worship.
[tense music playing]
Papa, what if…
What if Jaguar doesn't agree?
Well…
He should be reminded
that he is just a jaguar…
and I am a lion.
And the lion is the king of the jungle.
And I will eat him alive.
[tense music playing]
You know that you can't serve
two masters, Emilia.
Auntie, I'm not serving
either one of them.
I just don't tell Papa
that I'm meeting with Jaguar.
And same goes with Jaguar.
I don't tell him
what Papa and I talk about.
[Claire scoffs]
So, you're playing safe?
Well, you can say that.
I'll go to whoever will win
between Papa and Jaguar.
[Rufo] That old man has a lot of nerve.
Did he really expect you
to join forces with him?
The Ardientes are going down, Jaguar.
Did you see his grandson, the mayor?
He walked out.
He was shaken.
How can he possibly win?
Watch your tongue, Rufo.
That's still my son we're talking about.
But…
between the two of them,
who would you want to win?
It's Diego, right?
And yet he continues to reject your help.
Jaguar…
The Ardientes are
desperate to work with you.
But Diego's group keeps pushing you away.
What will you do?
Where will you stand?
Until a decision needs to be made…
I don't have to worry about that.
The only thing we should do
is get stronger.
That Madrigal. We need him in our group.
You should work on that.
Do you understand?
[tense music playing]
We signed a peace agreement.
Not a single one of
the Ardientes or their men
can get past this line, do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Carl, get into position.
[ominous music playing]
He's not one of the Ardientes, right?
He works for Jaguar.
Jaguar?
[ominous music playing]
Isn't that the group
fighting the Ardientes?
You're right, Madrigal.
They're a vicious group.
Who's that?
Jaguar's right-hand man. His name is Rufo.
Rufo?
Congressman, confirmed.
Jaguar has been watching Diego's camp.
Are those idiots
really going to join forces?!
Do you mean to tell me that Jaguar
and that snot-nosed Diego are teaming up?
What are you waiting for?
Bring me that man!
Yes, sir.
[ominous music playing]
Let's go.
Don't they work for the Ardientes?
[grunts, groans]
Don't!
Lower your guns.
Don't get involved.
-[groans]
-Let him be.
[grunts]
-[grunts] Take him inside.
-Get in!
Get in!
[suspenseful music playing]
Ivy? Ivy!
Ivy!
[unsettling music playing]
Ivy? Ivy!
Ivy?!
Hey, Arnaldo!
Ivy…
Have you found anything?
-Not yet, Mayor.
-Well, keep looking!
-Keep looking!
-[whispers] Emilia…
Hey! Arnaldo, what's going on?
-Ivy…
-What?
Ivy… Ivy…
-No, no, no.
-Can you please tell us…
-what's going on?
-No, no. Something--
Hey! Can you--
[stutters] Ivy…
-Something…
-What?!
-Something's happening.
-What going on with Ivy?
Something's hap--
[panting]
Are you back to your senses?
-[unsettling music playing]
-[heavy breathing]
Ivy.
What's with Ivy?!
Tell us what's bothering you!
Arnaldo!
Ivy… She is…
She's what? Tell us! She's what?
She's… uh--
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Do you want to get Ivy Aguas back?
Damn you! What do you want?!
Hey, come on!
Can you please tell us what's going on?
Face me by yourself.
Just you.
No Ardientes. No cops.
No pesky media.
Or else…
Ivy Aguas will die.
Hey! Psst!
What?
Arnaldo.
Arnaldo!
Did you see that?
Emilia, something is wrong.
What is happening again?
[phone ringing]
Listen to me. I'm the mayor of this town,
and I will not be threatened by nobody.
For all I know, you don't even have Ivy.
But don't worry.
Now, you have my attention.
I will track you down and kill you myself.
Do you hear me? Huh?
I'll kill you!
-I'll kill--
-[line drops]
[screams in frustration]
[grumbles]
No, no.
[grumbling]
[tense music playing]
[phone chimes]
[suspenseful music playing]
[mysterious caller]
Twenty million pesos, Mayor.
Or else, Ivy Aguas will die.
[suspenseful music playing]
No, no, no, no.
[panicked breathing]
Arnaldo?
Hey, son!
-What's going on?!
-Arnaldo!
-Arnaldo, hey!
Tell me. What's going on?
[tense music playing]
Arnaldo.
We are family, Arnaldo, okay?
Whatever is bothering you, I'm sure…
…your mother and your grandpa
can help you.
We'll do something about it.
-Yes!
-Okay?
[mysterious caller]
Face me by yourself. Just you.
No Ardientes. No cops.
Or else, Ivy Aguas will die.
Okay, uh… [clears throat]
Uh…
I'm okay.
Huh?
-Uh… Nothing's wrong.
-But you were just…
You were almost hysterical earlier.
What's happening, Arnaldo?
Who were you talking to on the phone?
Uh…
I'm sorry, but that was
just a business partner.
And…
We had a little disagreement.
But it's okay now.
What?!
All the while, you were
talking about business?
Yes.
Yes. Uh…
So, excuse me.
[unsettling music playing]
Business?
[sighs]
-[grunting, panting]
-[shushes]
Let him go.
[tense music playing]
Welcome, Rufo.
Sit down.
Would you like to have a drink?
You don't have to do that, Congressman.
You won't win me over
with your nice guy act.
Act?
You're mistaken, Rufo.
I don't do pretensions.
Actually…
I am the most straightforward person
you will meet in the world.
Why did you bring me here?
Well…
I wanted to talk to Jaguar.
[scoffs]
I'd like to offer him a deal.
But the thing is,
I know he would never agree,
knowing I would be the one talking to him.
That's why I brought you here.
Maybe…
Maybe you can find a way
to make it happen.
And…
the way I see it, the
easiest way to do that
would be to break Jaguar's trust.
Try to destroy his will.
Until eventually…
he decides to reach out to me.
Congressman.
You're talking to the wrong man.
[tense music playing]
Like I said, Rufo…
I am the most straightforward man
you will ever meet in the world.
Now…
What is it going to be?
[tense music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[mumbling] Plaza, plaza, plaza.
[Clara] Please double-check it
because the mayor needs this
by next week, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
[phone rings]
[Clara] Hello? Mayor?
Clara, prepare 20 million pesos.
[Clara] Twenty million, Mayor?
[Arnaldo] Yes, 20 million.
[Clara] But, Mayor, we have to
inform the congressman first.
Listen to me.
You don't need Grandpa's signature, right?
Just do as I say.
[unsettling music playing]
Ivy?
[suspenseful music playing]
Ivy!
[mumbles] Where are you?
Where…
[suspenseful music playing]
Hands up.
Uh… [laughs]
[Arnaldo grunts]
All right, all right.
[Arnaldo] But you'll regret this.
I don't know where you're
getting the guts to do this.
But you will regret this.
Do you hear me?
Do you hear me?! You will regret this!
[screams and grunts]
[suspenseful music playing]
[car engine revving]
[Jepoy] What did you two talk about?
Will you sell Jaguar out?
[Arthur] Think twice about
everything you're going to do.
You don't want to marry
a corpse, now do you?
[grunts]
Do you know what I do
to traitors like you?
I cut them in half.
[grunts and groans]
[Julio] I want you to do me a favor.
I want you to mount a manhunt
against this hoodlum Jaguar.
I want you to find him,
catch him, and kill him
ASAP.
[theme music playing]